<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>AzRoleWatcher</title><description>Continuously monitor roles and permissions in Microsoft Entra ID and Azure.</description><language>en</language><item><title>🆕 ADDED Azure role</title><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 03:42:33</pubDate><description><![CDATA[<b>Id:</b> 20cf746c-c765-402a-885e-c389c64478ce <br><b>Display name:</b> Azure Kubernetes Fleet Manager ABAC Custom Resources Reader <br><b>Description:</b> Allows read-only access to view Kubernetes custom resources on Azure Kubernetes Fleet Manager fleets. This role enables viewing custom resources without the ability to create, modify, or delete them. Applying this role at cluster scope will give read access to custom resources across all namespaces. More information on supported attributes for Attribute-Based Access Control (ABAC) conditions can be found under documentation at aka.ms/aks/abac/custom-resources/docs <br><b>Link:</b> https://management.azure.com/20cf746c-c765-402a-885e-c389c64478ce?api-version=2022-04-01]]></description></item><item><title>🆕 ADDED Azure role</title><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 03:42:33</pubDate><description><![CDATA[<b>Id:</b> 673366d4-9664-4020-b03b-b0093366bff9 <br><b>Display name:</b> Azure Kubernetes Fleet Manager ABAC Custom Resources Writer for Member Clusters <br><b>Description:</b> Allows write and delete access to manage Kubernetes custom resources on Azure Kubernetes Fleet Manager member clusters. This role enables creating, modifying, and deleting custom resources. Applying this role at cluster scope will give access to custom resources across all namespaces. More information on supported attributes for Attribute-Based Access Control (ABAC) conditions can be found under documentation at aka.ms/aks/abac/custom-resources/docs <br><b>Link:</b> https://management.azure.com/673366d4-9664-4020-b03b-b0093366bff9?api-version=2022-04-01]]></description></item><item><title>🆕 ADDED Azure role</title><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 03:42:33</pubDate><description><![CDATA[<b>Id:</b> a366d631-94bf-46bf-b4af-b38f28c80774 <br><b>Display name:</b> Defender for Storage Threat Protection <br><b>Description:</b> Microsoft Defender for Storage Threat Protection role - grants the permissions needed to enable/disable Defender for Storage Advanced Threat Protection at resource level. <br><b>Link:</b> https://management.azure.com/a366d631-94bf-46bf-b4af-b38f28c80774?api-version=2022-04-01]]></description></item><item><title>🆕 ADDED Azure role</title><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 03:42:33</pubDate><description><![CDATA[<b>Id:</b> e1663658-d5f7-4383-9afb-af9fdc9c5eae <br><b>Display name:</b> Azure Kubernetes Fleet Manager ABAC Custom Resources Reader for Member Clusters <br><b>Description:</b> Allows read-only access to view Kubernetes custom resources on Azure Kubernetes Fleet Manager member clusters. This role enables viewing custom resources without the ability to create, modify, or delete them. Applying this role at cluster scope will give read access to custom resources across all namespaces. More information on supported attributes for Attribute-Based Access Control (ABAC) conditions can be found under documentation at aka.ms/aks/abac/custom-resources/docs <br><b>Link:</b> https://management.azure.com/e1663658-d5f7-4383-9afb-af9fdc9c5eae?api-version=2022-04-01]]></description></item><item><title>🆕 ADDED Azure role</title><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 03:42:33</pubDate><description><![CDATA[<b>Id:</b> f82fbe13-0f98-4809-af81-b82c343db82f <br><b>Display name:</b> Device Update Contributor <br><b>Description:</b> Gives you full access to manage Device Update accounts, instances, and private endpoint connections <br><b>Link:</b> https://management.azure.com/f82fbe13-0f98-4809-af81-b82c343db82f?api-version=2022-04-01]]></description></item><item><title>🆕 ADDED Azure role</title><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 03:42:33</pubDate><description><![CDATA[<b>Id:</b> ff8eb232-5069-437e-94e5-31112ef30539 <br><b>Display name:</b> Azure Kubernetes Fleet Manager ABAC Custom Resources Writer <br><b>Description:</b> Allows write and delete access to manage Kubernetes custom resources on Azure Kubernetes Fleet Manager fleets. This role enables creating, modifying, and deleting custom resources. Applying this role at cluster scope will give access to custom resources across all namespaces. More information on supported attributes for Attribute-Based Access Control (ABAC) conditions can be found under documentation at aka.ms/aks/abac/custom-resources/docs <br><b>Link:</b> https://management.azure.com/ff8eb232-5069-437e-94e5-31112ef30539?api-version=2022-04-01]]></description></item></channel></rss>