<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>AzRoleWatcher</title><description>Continuously monitor roles and permissions in Microsoft Entra ID and Azure.</description><language>en</language><item><title>🆕 ADDED Azure role</title><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 10:13:12</pubDate><description><![CDATA[<b>Id:</b> df87f177-bb12-4db1-9793-a413691eff94 <br><b>Display name:</b> Container Registry Cache Rule Administrator <br><b>Description:</b> Create, Read, Update, and Delete Cache Rules in Container Registry. This role doesn't grant permissions to manage Credential Sets. <br><b>Link:</b> https://management.azure.com/df87f177-bb12-4db1-9793-a413691eff94?api-version=2022-04-01]]></description></item><item><title>🆕 ADDED Azure role</title><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 10:13:12</pubDate><description><![CDATA[<b>Id:</b> c357b964-0002-4b64-a50d-7a28f02edc52 <br><b>Display name:</b> Container Registry Cache Rule Reader <br><b>Description:</b> Read the configuration of Cache Rules in Container Registry. This permission doesn't grant permission to read Credential Sets. <br><b>Link:</b> https://management.azure.com/c357b964-0002-4b64-a50d-7a28f02edc52?api-version=2022-04-01]]></description></item><item><title>🆕 ADDED Azure role</title><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 10:13:12</pubDate><description><![CDATA[<b>Id:</b> f094fb07-0703-4400-ad6a-e16dd8000e14 <br><b>Display name:</b> Container Registry Credential Set Administrator <br><b>Description:</b> Create, Read, Update, and Delete Credential Sets in Container Registry. This role doesn't affect the needed permissions for storing content inside Azure Key Vault. This role also doesn't grant permissions to manage Cache Rules. <br><b>Link:</b> https://management.azure.com/f094fb07-0703-4400-ad6a-e16dd8000e14?api-version=2022-04-01]]></description></item><item><title>🆕 ADDED Azure role</title><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 10:13:12</pubDate><description><![CDATA[<b>Id:</b> 29093635-9924-4f2c-913b-650a12949526 <br><b>Display name:</b> Container Registry Credential Set Reader <br><b>Description:</b> Read the configuration of Credential Sets in Container Registry. This permission doesn't allow permission to see content inside Azure Key vault only the content inside Container Registry. This permission doesn't grant permission to read Cache Rules. <br><b>Link:</b> https://management.azure.com/29093635-9924-4f2c-913b-650a12949526?api-version=2022-04-01]]></description></item><item><title>🆕 ADDED Azure role</title><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 10:13:12</pubDate><description><![CDATA[<b>Id:</b> 8d7ecc5c-f27b-43cf-883f-46409d445502 <br><b>Display name:</b> Issue Contributor <br><b>Description:</b> Can read all issues data and update issues settings. <br><b>Link:</b> https://management.azure.com/8d7ecc5c-f27b-43cf-883f-46409d445502?api-version=2022-04-01]]></description></item></channel></rss>